
<Publish>
  <!--Id must be set in order to update existing mod. It is not required for publishing mod for the first time--> 
  <ModId Value="141486" />
  <!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
  <DisplayName Value="AdvancedTPM" />
  <!--Short description of the mod-->
  <ShortDescription Value="AdvancedTPM - Advanced Tax and Production Manager" />
  <!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
  <LongDescription>
Take Absolute Control of Your City's Economy

Advanced Tax and Production Manager (AdvancedTPM) is an all-in-one economic dashboard covering taxes, production, companies, residential zones, districts, and services.

## Residential Browser

Filter and sort every residential building in your city by density, level, district, theme, asset pack, occupancy, happiness, and more.

The browser supports all content without needing a mod update. Base Game buildings, DLC region packs, themed content, and custom creator packs all appear automatically. If a content pack provides a filter icon the mod uses it, exactly as it appears in the game menus. New packs added in future game updates will show up on their own.

- Native icon integration. Theme and pack filters pull icons directly from the game's internal image system.
- Pack placement counts. The summary table shows how many buildings from each installed content pack are on your map, split by density tier.
- Dual camera actions per row: jump to the building on the map, or focus it in the game info panel.
- 50 buildings per page for fast rendering in very large cities.
- Live updates pause when a row is expanded so the detail view stays stable.
- Intelligent asset resolution. The backend checks asset pack data, zone types, native DLC requirements, and Paradox Mods metadata so no custom building is missed.
- Smart name normalization. Internal PascalCase names are automatically split into readable text and redundant file tags are stripped so filter lists look clean.
- Multi-pack support. If an asset belongs to multiple packs the UI lines up all associated icons side-by-side.
- High-performance caching. Pack lookups are calculated once and cached for instant reuse, keeping navigation smooth.

## Tax and Production Dashboard

- Per-resource tax sliders for 50+ resources across raw materials, industrial goods, immaterial services, commercial retail, and entertainment.
- Real-time production and consumption bars with surplus and deficit indicators.
- Resources grouped by supply chain category: Agriculture, Forestry, Mining, Oil, Office, Entertainment, and Commercial.
- Per-resource and total tax income with in-game currency formatting.
- Workforce stats and demand signals per resource.

## Company Browser

- Sortable and filterable table by zone, profitability tier, profit range, or text search.
- Expand any row for brand name, address, level, zone, output and input resources, staffing bars, and full efficiency breakdown with CS2 icons, percentage impact, and cumulative efficiency score.
- Company happiness score in rows and detail panels. Score is estimated from efficiency, profit, staffing, and tax. The server provides an authoritative value when available.
- Signature building detection. All known DLC signature buildings are flagged and used by the Advisor.
- Click to jump the camera to any company building.

## Signature Buildings Tab

- Dedicated unified tab showing every signature building across commercial, residential, and service categories in one view.
- Full DLC landmark and prefab whitelist. No buildings are missed.
- Live tab badge showing the current count of signature buildings in your city.
- Signature buildings are fed into the Adaptive Learning Advisor when making tax recommendations.

## Districts Dashboard

- Reorderable metric cards. Drag to rearrange. Available cards: Education Levels, Properties, Demographics, Households, School Data, Health and Value, and Policies.
- Per-district demographics with age group bar (Children, Teens, Adults, Seniors) and resident, student, tourist, and homeless counts.
- Education level bars for both residents and workers.
- Property breakdown by type: Residential, Mixed, Commercial, Industrial, Office, and Storage.
- Household metrics: current vs capacity, average wealth, average income, and average rent.
- School data: Elementary, High School, College, and University enrollment vs capacity with availability percentage.
- Health and Value card: health status, crime risk, average land value, and average building level.
- Toggle district-level policies directly from the expanded panel.
- Rename districts in-game from the panel.
- GO button to jump the camera to any district.
- Sortable columns and card visibility settings with a reset to default option.
- Happiness aggregation per district.

## Services Browser

- Filterable panel for city service buildings with live metrics, grouped by service category.

## Auto-Tax Engine

- 6-factor scoring balancing profitability, happiness, production, demand, company count, and tax income.
- Per-resource min and max ranges. Lock specific resources from auto-adjustment.
- Adjustable speed to control how frequently the engine runs, from slow cautious changes to aggressive rapid tuning.
- Profitability weight slider for finer control over the scoring formula.
- Live status bar showing city happiness, how many resources were raised, lowered, or held each cycle, and average company profitability.

## Adaptive Learning Advisor

- Builds a learned profile for each resource tracking sensitivity, income response, company response, production impact, revenue efficiency, and volatility.
- Records a before snapshot when a tax rate changes, waits for an observation period, then scores the outcome.
- Confidence-weighted recommendations. The more data collected the stronger the influence on scoring.
- Full decision log showing what changed, the outcome score, and the reasoning.
- Persistent profiles saved to disk and loaded between sessions.

## Settings

- Full mod settings page in the game options menu with General, Auto-Tax, Advisor, Debug, and About groups.
- Movable and resizable window. Drag the panel anywhere and resize freely. Position and size are saved automatically.
- Panel opacity slider. Adjust the transparency of the mod window.
- Tips toggle for in-UI tooltips with production details and usage guidance.

## Under the Hood

- High-performance prefab caching. Asset pack lookups use a concurrent cache dictionary. Pack dependencies are calculated exactly once per asset and reused instantly for every subsequent lookup, eliminating main-thread CPU spikes.
- Deep ECS extraction. The backend checks AssetPackItem, falls back to SpawnableBuilding zone data, checks native DLC requirements, and queries Paradox Mods metadata to find creator display names. No custom building is missed.
- Smart name normalization. PascalCase internal names are automatically split into readable text and redundant tags like Asset, Pack, or Filter are stripped so every filter list looks clean.
- Multi-pack icon rendering. Pack icon URLs are parsed as comma-separated lists. If an asset belongs to multiple packs or themes the UI lines up all associated native icons side-by-side.

## Performance

Built for the Cohtml engine using direct-DOM manipulation. UI thread cost is approximately 1.3ms with no measurable impact on game FPS. Paginated lists and a concurrent prefab cache keep navigation instant in any city size.
  </LongDescription>
  <!--Thumbnail-->
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/resources.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/businesses.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/commercial.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/office.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/residential.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/services.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/signature.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/residental_sig.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/districts.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/district_settings.jpg" />

	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
  <Tag Value="" />
  <!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/advanced-tax-production-manager.1917448/" />
  <!--Version of the mod-->
  <ModVersion Value="1.1.4" />
  <!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
  <GameVersion Value="1.5.10f*" />
  <!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
  <Dependency Id="" />
  <!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
  <RequiredDLC Value="" />
  <!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
## v1.1.4 - The Residential and Custom Content Update

### New Features
- Residential Browser: A new dashboard to track all residential buildings, occupancy, and demographics across the city.
- Native Custom Content Tracking: Automatically tracks Base Game buildings, official DLCs, region packs, and Paradox Mods custom creator packs. No mod update needed for new content.
- Native Icon Integration: Theme and pack filters pull icons directly from the game's internal image system. DLC and creator pack icons display exactly as they appear in the game menus.
- Pack Placement Dashboard: Summary table showing how many residential buildings from each installed content pack are on the map, broken down by density.
- Dual Go Actions: Jump the camera to a building's physical location or focus the building in the native info panel.

### Performance and Stability
- Strict UI Pagination: Data tables now render exactly 50 rows per page, eliminating UI lag in massive cities.
- Auto-Pause Data Sync: Expanding a row in the browser pauses live updates for that element, keeping data stable while reading.
- Prefab Caching System: Concurrent caching for asset pack lookups reduces main-thread CPU spikes during UI generation.
- Smart Name Normalization: PascalCase asset names are automatically split into readable text and redundant file tags are stripped.
- Signature tab icon rendering fixed. Full DLC building whitelist complete.
- Fixed UI clipping in panel dropdowns.
- Fixed window dragging getting stuck after release.
- Resolved compilation errors in school, hospital, and garbage data extraction.

## v1.1.3 - Residential Browser and Custom Asset Tracking

### Added
- Residential Browser: Filterable and sortable panel for all residential zones.
- Custom asset pack detection and grouping with PackIcon headers.
- District-level demographics and household stats.

### Fixed
- Base Game icon now shows the correct Paradox Star icon for vanilla assets.
- Theme names for custom assets are preserved as authored.
- Zero-allocation buffer optimization for building data parsing.
	</ChangeLog>
  <!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/binded-zz/AdvancedTPM" />
  <!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
  <AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
