
<Publish>
  <!--Id must be set in order to update existing mod. It is not required for publishing mod for the first time--> 
  <ModId Value="141486" />
  <!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
  <DisplayName Value="AdvancedTPM" />
  <!--Short description of the mod-->
  <ShortDescription Value="AdvancedTPM - Advanced Tax &amp; Production Manager" />
  <!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
  <LongDescription>
	  Take Absolute Control of Your City's Economy
	  Advanced Tax &amp; Production Manager (AdvancedTPM) is an all-in-one economic dashboard designed to give you deep visibility into your supply chain and automate your tax rates without sacrificing a single frame.
	  Key Features:
	  Deep Economic Visualization: Track production, consumption, surplus, and deficits across all resource categories in real-time. See exactly what your city is overproducing or starving for.
	  Smart Auto-Taxing: Stop micromanaging sliders. The Auto-Tax system dynamically adjusts your tax rates based on city happiness, company profitability, and actual resource demand.
	  Advanced Browsers: Drill down into the details with comprehensive tracking for Companies, Districts, Residential zones, and Services. Find out exactly which businesses are thriving, and which are failing.
	  Signature Building Tracker: Unified view to track the status, efficiency, and worker counts of all your unlocked Signature Buildings.
	  Adaptive Learning System: An integrated advisor that learns from your city's economic shifts to help guide optimal tax directions.
	  Uncompromising Performance: Built specifically for the Cohtml engine. By utilizing 0ms latency direct-DOM manipulation, the mod boasts a microscopic ~1.3ms thread cost. Enjoy massive economic data tracking with absolutely zero impact on your game's FPS.



	  next update will be focused on adding more features and improving the rest of the service residential system but i will also continue to look for ways to optimize the performance of the mod.

	  For full details, screenshots and installation steps please see the project README or edit the mod page on the hosting site.
  </LongDescription>
  <!--Thumbnail-->
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/resources.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/businesses.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/commercial.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/office.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/residential.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/services.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/signature.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/districts.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/districts_expand.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/district_settings.jpg" />

	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
  <Tag Value="" />
  <!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/advanced-tax-production-manager.1917448/" />
  <!--Version of the mod-->
  <ModVersion Value="1.1.3" />
  <!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
  <GameVersion Value="1.5.8f1*" />
  <!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
  <Dependency Id="" />
  <!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
  <RequiredDLC Value="" />
  <!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
		<![CDATA[
## Changelog 1.1.3
- Internal deployment verification and minor updates

## Changelog 1.1.2 update to dotnet 4.8 
## Changelog 1.1.1
## v1.1.1 - Improved Performance and bug fixes used profiler to find bottlenecks and make fixes. this thing should fly now.
removed district happiness system couldnt get it to to work right or at least the way i wanted it too it was costing tons of cpu

## Changelog 1.1.0
## v1.1.0 - Districts Residential & Services Overhaul

### Added
- ** Districts Dashboard:** Complete overhaul featuring reorderable cards, settings gear, demographic metrics, and district-level policies.
- ** Happiness Aggregation:** Integrated happiness metrics into the Districts UI panel.
- ** Residential Browser:** Filterable UI for residential housing data (themes, densities, occupancy, etc.) complete with residents/employees columns and dynamic rows.
- ** Services Browser:** Filterable panel for tracking city service buildings with metrics.
- ** Advisor Panel Fixes:** Stabilized the layout of the adaptive learning advisor logs and UI components.


	]]></ChangeLog> 
  <!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/binded-zz/AdvancedTPM" />
  <!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
  <AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
